Enjoy.
Thank you.
Call if you need anything.
Monou?
Sorry.
I don't recall seeing that individual before.
Right. She's a new hire, named Takizawa.
I'm sorry, I should have introduced you.
She's a hard worker,
so please be easy on her.
Of course.
Sui.
I never imagined we'd reunite so quickly.
What an absolute surprise.
- Why...
- "Why"?
I work here.
Didn't my Hirose tell you?
You'd better not get in my way again.
I'll talk to you soon.
Hello?
This is Takizawa,
from Hirose Architects, speaking.
I forgot to inform you earlier,
but I will be your point of contact now.
What?
Please send any details for Hirose my way.
Or did you find issue corresponding with me?
No, not at all. I understand.
Thank goodness.
I am excited to coordinate
this project with you.
Have a wonderful day.
This is my proposed schedule for the day-of.
Here are your profiles
for all our guests that day,
as well as an emcee script.
Thank you. These are all incredibly detailed.
Thank you, Mr. Hoshina.
Send these over for Hirose
to look over as well.
Yes, sir.
I'll ask if there are any edits
to be made as well.
Thanks again.
Of course.
She works quick.
Someone's way too excited about this.
[Proposal - Monou]
[Proposal - Takizawa]
[Your file has been renamed]
Thanks for the file.
Monou.
Has Hirose gotten back to us
about the event?
Not yet.
I'll reach out about it again.
Too bad. He must be busy.
Let me know how it goes.
Yes, sir.
Everything all right?
Huh? Yeah, it's going fine.
But...
I want to chip away at this alone
for a little longer.
Okay.
[Sui Monou]
Takizawa. Has Idea gotten back to us
about the talk event?
I've tried contacting Monou,
but I haven't been able to reach her.
I see.
Thanks again.
Hirose.
I don't know if I should mention this, but...
I used to work at the same company as Monou.
Huh?
I'm sorry I didn't bring it up earlier.
But now, I can't help but worry.
Monou tends to keep problems to herself.
So, perhaps this delay
is for a similar reason.
Monou does seem to hold herself
quite responsible.
She likely hopes to deliver on her idea.
Even so, we are running short on time.
I know this may seem a bit forward,
but perhaps this would suffice?
[The Importance of Fluid Architecture]
This is your draft, Takizawa?
Yes.
I thought we could reach out to Idea,
and see what they think of this script.
I see.
That sounds like a good idea.
Let's try sending our draft to Monou.
Yes, sir.
Thanks again.
You have a girlfriend now, don't you?
Where did that come from?
Sui told me about the girl with the stalker.
And since you're escorting her home,
I assumed.
Her name is Mizuno, and I really... you know.
Listen.
That's not love, okay?
You're just pretending to be a hero.
You can't date every girl who relies on you.
What happens when someone else in trouble?
Will you date everyone you save?
Mao.
Listen to your heart already.
For the event, will these times work for you?
Yes, I believe so.
Likewise.
Is something the matter?
No, rather...
I apologize for troubling you with this.
Huh?
We constantly asked for confirmations.
I know it must have been bothersome.
Please send my regards to Mr. Hoshina.
Of course.
We were worried about
the lack of correspondence,
but you must have a lot on your plate.
Yes, my apologies.
Hirose.
I wish to speak about Monou.
It wouldn't be possible
to work with someone else from Idea, no?
That's a difficult ask.
She's their representative, not ours.
I don't exactly have a say here.
I thought so. I apologize for asking.
If you'd rather not work with her,
either Minagawa or myself can...
No, please. Anything but that.
She'll take everything from me again.
"Again"?
Monou...
She bossed me around
at our prior job together.
Everyone else knew she meant no harm,
so no one would step up to her.
I quit my previous job because of Monou.
Yet now, I have to face her again...
I understand your circumstances.
Let me think about this.
Can we discuss this tonight?
Perhaps over dinner?
Sorry, I have to take this.
Hello?
Almost had him.
Sorry, I know you're busy as is.
It's no problem. I'll look into it.
We have improved our designs
to create spaces of comfort.
A raised floor, among other design choices...
It seems Hirose hasn't arrived yet.
I see. Thank you.
The number you have called is currently...
She won't answer.
He's definitely late.
- Hello there.
- Hey, Matsubara.
The auditorium's packed. I'm impressed.
What's the matter?
Hirose hasn't arrived yet.
Huh? But we're almost ready for him.
Have you called him?
Yes, but my calls aren't going through.
Don't worry, we've prepared all we could.
Push comes to shove,
I'll hold a solo talk session.
You're on in fifteen minutes.
Thank you.
I'll be standing by here.
I'll try searching for him again.
I'm willing to go up there if necessary.
Then here, can you review the script?
Huh? O-Oh, seriously?
What should we do next?
Were you interested
in any of the stores I sent you?
Mao?
Sorry.
Monou's event is today.
Are you worried about how it'll go?
No.
So... what are we doing again?
Finding a place for desserts?
I'm not really an expert on sweet things.
Mao.
Do you...
Do you really love me?
Huh?
I'm anxious.
Dating you still feels like a dream.
Can you prove to me that this isn't one?
He hasn't signed in yet.
I see.
Thank you for checking.
Sorry, ma'am.
Takizawa?
Thank goodness, you made it.
Good to see you too, Sui.
Will Hirose be joining us soon?
My Hirose won't be joining us today.
- What do you mean?
- Was I not clear?
He's not coming.
I told him the talk
was delayed by half an hour.
Why?
This is work. We're on the job right now.
You absolute eyesore.
Flaunting your misfortune
to get all the guys.
Why is life going better for you?
That has nothing to do with this event.
You're free to accuse me as you wish.
But Hirose and the audience here
have no part in our squabble.
You still don't understand?
I'm only doing what'll hurt you most.
"Why"?
Blame your faulty body.
You brought misfortune to my life,
only for yourself to get away scot-free?
How awfully convenient for you.
I play no part
in how happy you are or aren't.
What?
No matter what else you say about my body,
I won't feel hurt, nor offended anymore.
You think you're so much better than me.
Let yourself be miserable, damn it!
I have every right to be more happy than you!
Monou!
Oh, um...
I'll make my excuses later.
For now, the auditorium.
Right this way.
Why the hell are you here?
Creating homes without preconceived notions
has been my aim for several years now.
Our discussion today
has been a wonderful opportunity
to refresh my beliefs.
These sorts of preconceived notions
are the result of history. Furthermore...
Thank you again.
I'm glad it was a success.
Great work, everyone.
Your talk today was spectacular.
I've called a taxi for you.
Takizawa.
You do not need to come in starting tomorrow.
Pardon?
I looked into your background.
And I do not wish to associate
with an individual like yourself.
Looked into what, exactly?
Our industry is tightly knit, you see.
So, I heard all about your ordeals
with the Himukai son.
You've misunderstood.
This woman screwed my life over.
It seems our perception of Monou
is nothing alike.
Monou is an important friend of mine,
who truly understands me.
Please do not bother her,
or associate with my company ever again.
Every damn time...
How can you all be tricked by this woman?
Fine. I've had enough.
I'm the only one who knows my own worth.
One day, you'll all see
how I'm far better than her.
A worthless, incompetent woman like you
will miserably cling to men all your life.
My condolences.
Are you all right?
Yes, sorry.
The apology is mine to make.
Our mistake caused you to experience
such harassment.
It's no worries.
Seeing the smiles of our audience today
was enough to wash away the bad memories.
Let's celebrate this event's success
over dinner sometime.
How does next Thursday sound?
Next Thursday...
Yes, that sounds great.
I heard a loud noise. Is everything okay?
Yeah, sorry.
Mao, your foot.
There, all patched up.
Thanks for the help.
It's the least I can do
for all you've done for me.
Actually...
- See you!
-You were the one who saved me first.
You okay?
Here, sit.
I'm fine.
You might feel fine now.
But sometimes the pain only springs up later.
You have to treasure yourself.
Okay?
It was a bad day back at home.
I was chased out on my birthday,
so I ran to Erika's to hide.
I was honestly depressed,
so your care really saved me.
All I did was give you a bandage.
But I see.
So, it was your birthday that day.
Your birthday is also coming up, isn't it?
Yeah. I'm surprised you know.
Erika mentioned it.
Are you eating dinner with her that day?
No. Hirose invited me out
to celebrate the success of today's event.
I see.
If it starts hurting,
go to the hospital, okay?
- Good night.
- Night.
Hirose?
I wasn't ever kind to you.
Whether you mention your infertility or not
is entirely your choice.
Just like how it's your partner's choice
to decide how to respond.
I didn't care if your kindness
was out of pity.
Happiness is a difficult thing, isn't it?